Robert Isaac Ebita Cortez

WEB DESIGNER

About Me

I am a Web Designer, UI/UX Designer, and Front-End Developer with a background in management and graphic design. Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and MERN-Stack, I create user-centered, visually appealing websites that align with client goals and branding, blending functionality with aesthetics for a satisfying user experience.

Employment History

Freelance Web Designer

JUNE 2024 - PRESENT

Online

- Configured over twenty personalized templates using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, whilst incorporating React.js for interactive features, all of which align with the clients' personal brands and career goals.
- Led consultations with over twenty clients to design tailored, visually appealing websites aligned with brand identity and client feedback.

Accommodation Assistant, RS Cortez: Room For Rent

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

South Cotabato, Philippines (Hybrid)

 Assisted an average thirty occupants weekly with requests and concerns, while networking to attract students and managing financial records for the boarding house.

Freelance Graphic Designer

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Sydney, Australia (Hybrid)

 Designed over thirty posters and logos for events and seminars using Adobe Illustrator and Canva.

Secretary, RS Cortez: Fresh & Frozen

MAY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2021

South Cotabato, Philippines (Hybrid)

- Managed administrative tasks, coordinated orders, organized records, and maintained inventory to ensure smooth operations, while accompanying the CEO on ten business trips monthly for the first year.
- Facilitated CEO communications by handling an average of fifty calls weekly, managing emails, and engaging with clients, while providing on-site support for logistics and meetings.

Education

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, Uplift Code Camp

MAY 2024 - OCTOBER 2024

Online

- Developed projects using Vanilla JavaScript and MERN Stack, gaining practical experience in full-stack web development and developing a proficient understanding and problem solving skills in web development.
- Engaged in career development training, enhancing professional skills and industry readiness.

BS Information Technology, Mapua Malayan Digital College

SEPTEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

Online

Majoring in software development, I study the basics of computer programming, while
engaging with engaging in coursework to develop problem-solving skills applicable to
real-world IT environments.

Details

South Cotabato, Philippines

09856528649

isaacebitacortez@gmail.com

Links

 LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/isaac uiux

 GitHub https://github.com/lsaacCortezUI UX

 E-Portfolio https://ic-dc-webdesign.netlify.app

Skills

- Frontend Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, React.js)
- Backend Development (Node.js, Express.js)
- Database Management (MongoDB)
- UI/UX Design (Draw.io, Figma, Wireframing, Responsive Design)
- Graphic Design (Canva, Adobe Illustrator)
- Problem Solving & Communication (Analysis, Client Communication, Public Speaking)

References

Mary Jerely Laguda
 Telus International Philippines
 Senior Software Engineer
 09190978700